# Mark Mulligan

Phone: (817) 504-5426 | Email: mark.mulligan.jr1@gmail.com

LinkedIn: www.linkedin.com/in/mark-mulligan-50

Portfolio: <a href="https://markmulligan.dev">https://markmulligan.dev</a>

GitHub: <a href="https://github.com/Mark-Mulligan">https://github.com/Mark-Mulligan</a>

Mark is a full stack developer experienced in React.js, Python, Node.js and Postgres. Currently, Mark works for a company that uses AI to reduce false motion alarms on security cameras. Outside of his day job, Mark works with a fast growing fine arts management software for school district and is building a Japanese language learning app.

### **TECHNICAL SKILLS**

React.js, Next.js, Typescript, Node.js, Python, Postgres, AWS, Tailwind, Docker, Github Actions

#### **EXPERIENCE**

## Full Stack Developer - Evolon Technologies

February 2022 - Present

- React / Typescript / Python / Node.js / Postgres
- Created and designed system for handling live streaming from cameras, creating opportunity for new markets and a 40% increase in revenue for the underling product
- Created real time remote configuration system for our camera software, leading to a 120% increase in cameras using our product.
- Made significant contributions for a new pro monitoring solution that provides a new addressable market as well as a higher margin product offering
- Award winner of Security Industry Assoication's 25 on the rise (2024)
  https://www.securityindustry.org/rise/25-on-the-rise/25-on-rise-honorees

# Full Stack Developer - Visual Storage Intelliegence

May 2020 - February 2022

- Python / React / Node.js / MSSQL
- Developed system to automate new customer setup, reducing setup time by 50%
- Improved security in application by developing a system for two factor authentication

### ADDITONAL EXPERIENCE

### Front end Developer - Presto Assistant

July 2023-Present

- React, Typescript, MUI, and GraphQL <a href="https://www.presto-assistant.com">https://www.presto-assistant.com</a>
- Presto Assistant is a fine arts management software used by over 100 school districts nationwide, helping teachers manage inventory, communicate, and handle finances.

# **Developer - Fluency Forge**

June 2023-Present

- Next.js, Tailwind, and Supabase <a href="https://www.fluencyforge.com">https://www.fluencyforge.com</a>
- Language learning application design to help you read and learn Japensese characters

### **EDUCATION**

**Certificate, Full Stack Web Development** – Southern Methodist Unversity **Bachelor of Arts, Music Education** – University of North Texas

Dallas, TX Denton, TX